{
    "subject": "resource/Eibenstock_Dam",
    "predicate": "ontology/river",
    "object": "resource/Zwickau_Mulde",
    "human_readable": "The Eibenstock Dam is fed by the Zwickau Mulde.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9555754661560059,
            "question": "Is the Zwickau Mulde a source of water for the Eibenstock Dam?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6840663552284241,
            "question": "Where is the Eibenstock Dam located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6361730098724365,
            "question": "The Zwickau Mulde is responsible for supplying water to which dam?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5680285692214966,
            "question": "Name a water source for the Eibenstock Dam."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49634772539138794,
            "question": "What river feeds the Eibenstock Dam?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49044519662857056,
            "question": "Which river flows into the Eibenstock Dam?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41233766078948975,
            "question": "What is the name of the river that flows into the Eibenstock Dam?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4117421805858612,
            "question": "What body of water feeds the Eibenstock Dam?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3738038241863251,
            "question": "What is the name of the river that supplies water to the Eibenstock Dam?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34062156081199646,
            "question": "What river supplies the Eibenstock Dam with water?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The Eibenstock Dam is fed by the Zwickau Mulde.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7126_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the river that supplies water to the Eibenstock Dam?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7126_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What body of water feeds the Eibenstock Dam?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7126_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the river that flows into the Eibenstock Dam?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7126_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7126_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7126_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7126_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7126_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7126_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7126_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7126_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7126_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7126_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7126_68.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation:\n\nThe text mentions that the Zwickauer Mulde has two source rivers, the Red Mulde and the White Mulde. Both of these source rivers empty into the Muldenberg valley dammed reservoir after approx. 3 km. Then, it says that the Zwickauer Mulde emerges from this reservoir and flows to Eibenstock, where it empties into the largest reservoir in Saxony, the Eibenstock dam.\n\nThis suggests that the Zwickau Mulde does indeed feed into the Eibenstock Dam. Therefore, the answer is \"yes\"."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement. Specifically, they mention the Zwickauer Mulde and its relation to the Eibenstock dam. For instance, one document states: \"The Zwickauer Mulde emerges from this reservoir [Eibenstock dam] and flows mostly northeast through the forested region of Vogtland and Erzgebirge, until it empties into the largest reservoir in Saxony, the Eibenstock dam.\" This indicates that the Eibenstock Dam is fed by or related to the Zwickauer Mulde, supporting the given triple."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n     \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}